Indiana University Vice President and Chancellor's records, 1963-1976 C132
Indiana University Archives
- Administrative subject files, 1963-1976 (Box 1)
  - Higher Education Commission, Degree Proposals, 1974-1975 (Box 10)
  - Higher Education and National Affairs, 1974-1976 (Box 10)
  - Home Economics, 1970-1972 (Box 10)
  - Honors Committee, 1963-1970 (Box 10)
  - Honors Division (Box 10)
    - 1970-1972 (Box 10)
    - 1972-June 1975 (Box 10)
  - Hoosier Heritage Hall Advisory Committee, 1966-1970 (Box 10)
  - Horizons of Knowledge Committee, 1963-1970 (Box 10)
  - Horizons of Knowledge Fund, 1972 (Box 10)
  - House Planning Committee, 1969 (Box 10)
  - Housing, 1970-1975 (Box 10)
  - Hughes, Charles, 1973 (Box 10)
  - Human Growth, Center for, 1970-1972 (Box 10)
  - Human Relations, Director of, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Humanistic Studies, 1972-1975 (Box 10)
  - Improvement of Teaching, Committee on, 1955-1970 (Box 10)
  - Indiana Author s Day Award Committee, 1967-1970 (Box 10)
  - Indiana Daily Student, 1970-1972 (Box 10)
  - Indiana Language Program (Box 10)
    - General, 1971 (Box 10)
    - Council on Research and Experimentation, 1967-1968 (Box 10)
    - Working Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 10)
    - Advisory Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 10)
  - Indiana Memorial Union (Box 10)
    - 1969-1972 (Box 10)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 10)
  - Indiana Interest Research Group (INPIRG) (Box 10)
    - General (Box 10)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 10)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 10)
    - Funding Proposal, Board of Trustees, January 19, 1973 (Box 10)
  - Indiana University Foundation, 1971 (Box 10)
  - Indiana University Press, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
  - Inquiries, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Instructional Systems in Teacher Education, INSITE, 1969 (Box 10)
  - Insurance (Box 10)
    - 1970-1972 (Box 10)
    - 1972-1974 (Box 10)
  - International Studies (Box 10)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 10)
    - 1972-1975 (Box 10)
  - Institutional Research, Office of (Box 10)
    - 1970-1974 (Box 10)
    - 1973-1975 (Box 10)
  - Intramural Facilities, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - Items for Board of Trustees Agenda, October 26, 1972 (Box 10)
  - IU Operating Directive, 1972 (Box 10)
  - I.U.P.U.I., 1971-1975 (Box 10)
  - J Courses, 1971-1972 (Box 10)
  - Job Applications, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Jones, Ted, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Jordan River, 1972 (Box 10)
  - Journalism Department, 1971-1975 (Box 10)
  - Junior Division Advisory Board, 1969 (Box 11)
  - Kagaon-Kans, Eva, 1972-1974 (Box 11)
  - Kiyose, Gisaburo, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
  - Labor Education, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Language Requirement, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Latinos, 1972-1975 (Box 11)
  - Latinos - Revista Chicano-Riquena, v. 1, no. 1-2; v. 2, no. 1 (Box 11)
  - Law, School of, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Law Visiting Committee, Bloomington, 1969 (Box 11)
  - Library (Box 11)
    - 1970-1972 (Box 11)
    - April 1972-May 1974 (Box 11)
  - Library Committee (Box 11)
    - 1969 (Box 11)
    - 1971-1975 (Box 11)
  - Life Insurance, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Life Insurance for Center Employees, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Lilly-Dickey Committee, 1969 (Box 11)
  - Lilly Endowment, Inc., 1974-1975 (Box 11)
  - Living Learning Center, 1971-1975 (Box 11)
  - Linguistics, 1972-1975 (Box 11)
  - Lock-in, May 1969 (Box 11)
  - Long Distance Calls, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Long-Range Plan for Bloomington Campus, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Long-Range Planning (Box 11)
    - General, 1973 (Box 11)
    - Confidential, 1973 (Box 11)
    - University, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Long-Range Planning Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Major Gifts Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
  - Majority, Age of, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Majority, Change in the age of, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Management Information System, 1969 (Box 11)
  - Management Information System, 1972-1975 (Box 11)
  - Martin, Sandra, Grievance Case- Personnel, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Maternity Leave Policy, 1971-1972 (Box 11)
  - Materials Storage, Committee on, 1969 (Box 11)
  - Mathematics Department, 1971-1972 (Box 11)
  - Medical Science Program Ad Hoc Committee, Bloomington, 1971 (Box 11)
  - Medicine, 1972-1975 (Box 11)
  - Memorial Hall, 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Memorials, 1972-1974 (Box 11)
  - Mental Retardation, 1971 (Box 11)
  - Mid-September Paycheck, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Military Science, 1973-1975 (Box 11)
  - Minimum Enrollments (Box 11)
    - 1972 (Box 11)
    - 1973 (Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 11)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 11)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 11)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 11)
  - Model City, 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Moore, Milton, 1971 (Box 11)
  - Moratorium, 1969 (Box 11)
    General
    Includes photocopy of AAUP Bulletin, Summer 1968 article, "Statement on Faculty Participation in Strikes."
  - Moratorium on Staffing, 1972-1975 (Box 11)
  - M.U.C.I.A. (Midwest University Consortium for International Activities, Inc.) (Box 11)
    - 1971 (Box 11)
    - 1972-1975 (Box 11)
  - Music, School of (Box 11)
    - 1969-1972 (Box 11)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 11)
    - 1974-1976 (Box 11)
  - Musical Arts Center (Box 11)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 11)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Musical Arts Center Advisory Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 11)
  - Musical Arts Center Sculpture Committee, Ad Hoc, 1968-1969 (Box 11)
  - NABT Stationary, 1970 (Box 11)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC) (Box 12)
    - 1970 (Box 12)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 12)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 12)
  - National Science Foundation, 1971-1974 (Box 12)
  - Natural Areas, University Committee on, 1969 (Box 12)
  - Near Eastern Language and Literature, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Notices of Non-reappointment, 1971-1973 (Box 12)
  - New Course and Program Development (Box 12)
    - General, 1973 (Box 12)
    - Biology-Liberal Arts, 1974-1975 (Box 12)
    - Medicine-Science, 1974-1975 (Box 12)
  - October 1969 (Box 12)
  - Old Library Building Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 12)
  - Ombudsman, 1970-1974 (Box 12)
  - Operating Budget, 1970 (Box 12)
  - Operation Empty Chair, 1974-1975 (Box 12)
  - Optometry, 1971-1975 (Box 12)
  - Optometry Structural Review Committee, Ad Hoc, 1969 (Box 12)
  - O.S.H.A., 1974-1975 (Box 12)
  - OSUP (Ohio State University Poll, October 1972 (Box 12)
  - Oukhtomsky, Wladimir, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Outdoor Recreation, Committee for Research, 1969 (Box 12)
  - Outdoor Swimming Pool Committee, 1963-1971 (Box 12)
  - Outside Offers to Faculty (Box 12)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 12)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 12)
  - Overdrafts in Budget Lines, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Overseas Study, 1972-1976 (Box 12)
  - Parking (Box 12)
    - 1969-1972 (Box 12)
    - 1972-1975 (Box 12)
  - Parking Appeals Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 12)
  - Parking Study Committee, 1969-1971 (Box 12)
  - Past and Future Commitments, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Patten Foundation Committee (Box 12)
    - 1966-1970 (Box 12)
    - 1970-1975 (Box 12)
  - Paychecks, 1971 (Box 12)
  - Payment of Fringe Benefits (Box 12)
    - April 27, 1972 (Box 12)
    - July 11, 1972 (Box 12)
    - October 15, 1974 (Box 12)
  - Payroll Procedures for Academic Assistants, 1973 (Box 12)
  - Personal (Box 12)
    - 1969-1975 (Box 12)
    - 1970-1975 (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box 12)
  - Philosophy, 1971-1975 (Box 12)
  - Physical Plant, 1969-1975 (Box 12)
  - Physical Plant Task Force, APC, 1973 (Box 13)
  - Physics, 1970-1972 (Box 13)
  - Planned Parenthood, May 1972-April 1974 (Box 13)
  - Plant Sciences, 1972-1975 (Box 13)
  - Policy Advisory Committee, Indiana State Plan Study Design, 1966-1967; undated (Box 13)
  - Political Activity, 1970-1973 (Box 13)
  - Political Science (Box 13)
    - 1969-1972 (Box 13)
    - 1971-1975 (Box 13)
  - Poynter Center, 1971-1974 (Box 13)
  - Preparation of Non-General Fund Budget Requests, 1973 (Box 13)
  - President Nixon, 1970-1972 (Box 13)
  - President's Council on Humanities, 1973 (Box 13)
  - President's Council on Social Science, 1973 (Box 13)
  - President s Office, 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - Price Increase, 1974 (Box 13)
  - Printing and Duplicating, 1969-1972 (Box 13)
  - Printing and Duplicating Advisory Committee, 1970 (Box 13)
  - Promotions (Box 13)
    - 1969-1971 (Box 13)
    - 1971 (Box 13)
    - 1972, (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - Proposals, undated (Box 13)
  - Psychology, 1971-1975 (Box 13)
  - Public and Environmental Affairs, School of, 1973-1975; (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - Public Performance Committee (Box 13)
    - 1970-1972 (Box 13)
    - 1971 (Box 13)
  - Radio and Television, 1971-1975 (Box 13)
  - Rafalko (Box 13)
  - Real Estate, 1971-1975 (Box 13)
  - Records and Admissions (Box 13)
    - 1970-1972 (Box 13)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 13)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 13)
  - Recruitment, 1972-1974 (Box 13)
  - Recycling, 1971-1973 (Box 13)
  - Redbud, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Reference Letters, 1969-1975 (Box 13)
  - Regional Campuses (Box 13)
    - 1969-1971 (Box 13)
    - 1972-1975 (Box 14)
  - Registrar, 1973-1975 (Box 14)
  - Registration, 1970 (Box 14)
  - Registration, 1972-1975 (Box 14)
  - Releasing 80% of Funds, 1973 (Box 14)
  - Religious Studies Department, 1971 (Box 14)
  - Reports, 1971-1973; (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Reports, Bloomington Campus Clerical Staff, 1964 (Box 14)
  - Research and Advanced Studies (Box 14)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 14)
    - 1972-1975 (Box 14)
  - Research Associates, 1970-1971 (Box 14)
  - Research Committee (Box 14)
    - General (Box 14)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 14)
  - Research Computing Center, November 1971-February 1973 (Box 14)
  - Research and Development (Box 14)
    - 1970-1975 (Box 14)
    - 1972-1974 (Box 14)
  - Research in Outdoor Recreation Committee, 1970 (Box 14)
  - Residency, 1971-1974 (Box 14)
  - Residential Colleges, 1967-1986 (Box 14)
  - Resignations and Terminations, Faculty, 1969 (Box 14)
  - Retirement, 1971-1975 (Box 14)
  - Retiring Faculty, 1972-1975 (Box 14)
  - Retiring Faculty Reception, 1970-1972 (Box 14)
  - Roache, Addison, Memorial Fund Committee, 1972 (Box 14)
  - R.O.T.C., 1971-1975 (Box 14)
  - Sabbatical Leave, 1972-1975 (Box 14)
  - Sabbatical Leaves Committee, 1970 (Box 14)
  - Safety (Box 14)
    - 1970-1972 (Box 14)
    - 1972-1974 (Box 14)
  - Safety Meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 14)
  - Salary Adjustments for Change in Life Insurance, March 22, 1972 (Box 14)
  - Salary Adjustments for Change in Life Insurance, Correction, March 29, 1972 (Box 14)
  - Salary Increment Money, 1973 (Box 14)
  - Salary Letters, 1972 (Box 14)
  - Salary Letters and Rates, 1976 (Box 14)
  - Sale of Instructional Materials by Departments, 1974 (Box 14)
  - S and E Travel Telephones and Xerox, 1973 (Box 14)
  - Schecterman, Bernard (Box 14)
  - Schedule Committee (Box 14)
    - General, 1973 (Box 14)
    - Bloomington, 1970 (Box 14)
  - Schedule 4 of Biennial Budget Request, 1972 (Box 14)
  - Scholarships and Financial Aid, Committee on, 1969 (Box 14)
  - Scholarships and Financial Aids (Box 15)
    - 1970-1972 (Box 15)
    - 1972-1974 (Box 15)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 15)
  - School Science Advisory Committee, 1959-1971 (Box 15)
  - Schneider, Joseph, 1973-1974 (Box 15)
  - Schultz, Beatrice, 1970-1971 (Box 15)
  - Science Advisory Committee, 1972 (Box 15)
  - Science Advisory Committee, 1970-1975 (Box 15)
  - Scrimgeour, Gary, 1969 (Box 15)
  - Search and Screen Committee for Dean of Jr. Division, 1969 (Box 15)
  - Search and Screen Committee for Dean of the College of Arts and Sciences, 1969 (Box 15)
  - Secretariat, 1969 (Box 15)
  - Self-Study, Advisory Committee for the University, 1964-1967 (Box 15)
  - Self-Study, University Committee on Teaching Task Force, 1960-1966 (Box 15)
  - Sesquicentennial Campaign, 1970-1974 (Box 15)
  - Sesquicentennial Funds, 1970 (Box 15)
  - Sesquicentennial Requests for Funds, 1968-1971 (Box 15)
  - Slavic Language, 1970-1972 (Box 15)
  - Social Events, 1973-1974 (Box 15)
  - Social Service, 1973 (Box 15)
  - Sociology (Box 15)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 15)
    - 1972-1974 (Box 15)
  - Space Needs, 1971 (Box 15)
  - Spanish and Portuguese, 1970-1972 (Box 15)
  - SPEA, Self-Study, 1975 (Box 15)
  - Speakers, 1970-1971 (Box 15)
  - Speech Department, 1971-1972 (Box 15)
  - Staff Meetings, 1972 (Box 15)
  - Staff News, 1974-1976 (Box 15)
  - Students, 1969-1971 (Box 15)
  - Student Academic Appointments and the Fair Labor Standards Act, April 23, 1971 (Box 15)
  - Student Appointments, June 16, 1971 (Box 15)
  - Student Activities, Committee on, 1969 (Box 15)
  - Student Activities, December 1970-July 1973 (Box 15)
  - Student Affairs Committee, December 1972 (Box 15)
  - Student Conduct Committee, 1969 (Box 15)
  - Student Conduct Code Proposed Changes, Board of Trustees, January 19, 1973 (Box 15)
  - Student Correspondence (Box 15)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 15)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 15)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 15)
    - 1971-1974 (Box 15)
  - Student Demands, May 1969 (Box 15)
  - Students, Doctoral, 1968-1974 (Box 15)
  - Student Government (Box 15)
    - General, 1972-1974 (Box 15)
  - Student Government Audit, 1969-1972 (Box 15)
  - Student Health Service (Box 15)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 15)
    - 1972-1974 (Box 15)
  - Student Legal Advisor, 1970-1972 (Box 16)
  - Student Legal Services, 1972-1975 (Box 16)
  - Student Publications Board, 1969 (Box 16)
  - Student Unrest, May 11, 1970 (Box 16)
  - Summer Appointments (Box 16)
    - 1973 (Box 16)
    - 1974 (Box 16)
    - 1975 (Box 16)
  - Summer Departmental Fee Remission Awards, 1972 (Box 16)
  - Summer Departmental Fee Remissions, 1973 (Box 16)
  - Summer Research, 1972-1973 (Box 16)
  - Summer Salaries, 1972-1973 (Box 16)
  - Summer Session (Box 16)
    - 1972 (Box 16)
    - 1973 (Box 16)
  - Summer Sessions (Box 16)
    - 1969-1972 (Box 16)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 16)
    - 1974 (Box 16)
    - 1975 (Box 16)
  - Summer Session Budgets (Box 16)
    - General, 1973 (Box 16)
    - Requests from WBS, 1974 (Box 16)
  - Susan Butler and Clara Goodbody Awards Committee, 1964-1970 (Box 16)
  - Surveys, 1971 (Box 16)
  - Task Force on Energy Conservation, 1974 (Box 16)
  - Task Force on Placement Bureaus, 1973 (Box 16)
  - Task Force on Racism, 1971-1973 (Box 16)
  - Teacher Education Advisory Committee, 1969 (Box 16)
  - Teaching Awards (Box 16)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - 1972-1975 (Box 16)
  - Teaching Evaluation (Box 16)
    - 1969-1971 (Box 16)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 16)
  - Teaching Load, 1970-1974 (Box 16)
  - Teaching Loads, 1970-1972 (Box 16)
  - Telecommunications, 1972-1975 (Box 16)
  - Telephone Services, 1972-1975 (Box 16)
  - Tenure, 1972-1973 (Box 16)
  - Tenure, Specific Cases, 1972-1973 (Box 16)
  - Tenure and Retirement, 1971 (Box 16)
  - Thank You's, 1969-1972 (Box 16)
  - Theater and Drama Department, 1971-1972 (Box 16)
  - Timing of the 1972-73 Operating Budget, 1971 (Box 16)
  - Transportation, 1972-1975 (Box 16)
  - Travel, 1971-1975 (Box 16)
  - Travel Reimbursement, 1972 (Box 16)
  - Travel Expanse Reimbursement, 1972 (Box 16)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1970-1972 (Box 16)
  - Turner, Robert (Box 16)
    - 1970-1972 (Box 16)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 16)
  - Turner vs. Trustees, May-August 1972 (Box 16)
  - Undergraduate Education, 1970-1972 (Box 16)
  - Undergraduate Teaching, September-December 1973 (Box 16)
  - Union, Wage Proposals, etc., 1971 (Box 16)
  - Union Board (Box 16)
    - 1971-1975 (Box 16)
    - 1972-1974 (Box 16)
  - University Club, 1971 (Box 16)
  - University Division (Box 16)
    - 1970-1972 (Box 16)
    - 1972-1975 (Box 16)
    - 1975 (Box 16)
  - University Division Advisory Board Committee, 1971 (Box 16)
  - University Extension, 1968-1970 (Box 16)
  - University Student Broadcast Board of Directors, 1970 (Box 16)
  - Upward Bound, 1972 (Box 17)
  - Urban Affairs (Box 17)
    - 1971 (Box 17)
    - 1973 (Box 17)
  - Urban Affairs Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 17)
  - Vacant Budget Lines, 1971 (Box 17)
  - Veterans, 1974 (Box 17)
  - Vice-Comm., 1973 (Box 17)
  - Vietnam, ca. 1969 (Box 17)
  - Visitation, 1968-1970 (Box 17)
  - Visitors, 1970-1972 (Box 17)
  - Wage Freeze (Box 17)
    - General, 1971-1972 (Box 17)
    - Memos from Robert Turner, 1971 (Box 17)
    - Memos from Byrum Carter, August, 1971 (Box 17)
    - September 1971 (Box 17)
    - Adjustments, 1971 (Box 17)
    - Price, 1971 (Box 17)
    - Recommendations, 1971 (Box 17)
    - Women, 1971 (Box 17)
  - Water Tower, 1974 (Box 17)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1962-1972 (Box 17)
  - Wells, Award, 1970-1973 (Box 17)
  - Wells, Recognition Award Committee, 1970 (Box 17)
  - Williams Report, 1972 (Box 17)
  - Winter Session, 1972-1974 (Box 17)
  - WIUS Advisory Committee, 1969 (Box 17)
  - Women, 1972-1973 (Box 17)
  - Women's Affairs (Box 17)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 17)
    - 1973-1975 (Box 17)
  - Women's Athletics, 1973-1974 (Box 17)
  - Women's Studies (Box 17)
    - Appendices, 1973-1975 (Box 17)
    - Fact Sheet, 1976 (Box 17)
    - Certificate Proposal, undated (Box 17)
  - Your University (Box 17)
    - Interim Board, 1969-1971 (Box 17)
    - Publication, 1970-1972 (Box 17)
  - Y105 exam questions (Box 17)
  - Zoology, October 1971-1975 (Box 17)
- Logs, 1968-1973 (Box 17)
  - November 9, 1967-August 29, 1968 (Box 17)
  - August 30, 1968-April 8, 1969 (Box 17)
  - April 9, 1969-November 7, 1969 (Box 18)
  - November 10, 1969 (Box 18)
  - February 2, 1970-March 31, 1970 (Box 18)
  - March 23, 1970-May 15, 1970 (Box 18)
  - May 16, 1970-July 15, 1970 (Box 18)
  - July 16, 1970-September 11, 1970 (Box 18)
  - December 1, 1970-Febuary 26, 1971 (Box 18)
  - Mar. 1, 1971-April 30, 1971 (Box 18)
  - May 3, 1971-July 30, 1971 (Box 18)
  - August 2, 1971-October 15, 1971 (Box 18)
  - July 14, 1972- July -25, 1972 (Box 18)
  - July 26, 1972-August 2, 1972 (Box 18)
  - August 3, 1972-August 18, 1972 (Box 18)
  - August 21, 1972-August 31, 1972 (Box 18)
  - September 1, 1972-September 6, 1972 (Box 18)
  - September 7, 1972-September 12, 1972 (Box 18)
  - September 13, 1972-September 20, 1972 (Box 18)
  - September 21, 1972-October 3, 1972 (Box 18)
  - October 4, 1972-October 12, 1972 (Box 18)
  - October 13, 1972-October 23, 1972 (Box 18)
  - October 24, 1972-October 30, 1972 (Box 19)
  - October 31, 1972-November 6, 1972 (Box 19)
  - November 7, 1972-November 16, 1972 (Box 19)
  - November 17, 1972-November 27, 1972 (Box 19)
  - November 27, 1972-December 5, 1972 (Box 19)
  - December 6, 1972-December 11, 1972 (Box 19)
  - December 12, 1972-December 21, 1972 (Box 19)
  - December 1972-January 1973, (2 folders) (Box 19)
  - January 1973, (2 folders) (Box 19)
  - February 1973, (1 folders) (Box 19)
  - February 1973, (2 folders) (Box 20)
  - March 1973, (3 folders) (Box 20)
  - April 1973, (3 folders) (Box 20)
  - May 1973 (Box 20)
  - November 1973 (Box 20)
  - December 1973 (Box 20)
  - Restricted Materials (Box 21)